Hi!
In this video clip, I will be talking about using a drywall screw gun.
When we are screwing in drywall, we want to make sure that the screw just leaves a dimple in the paper for the drywall.
We don’t want the screw to go all the way through.
If you are using a regular drill, some times it can take a little while to get the hang of it.
The way that you set this drywall screw gun is you turn this collar on the end of the drill.
And if you take a look at the picture here, if you turn it to the left it is going to leave the screw out further.
If you turn it to the right, it is going to sink it in a little bit further.
So you are going to have to use a few test screws; screw it in.
If it is not far enough, tighten it up and screw it in some more.